Scott Hoecker

1542 N. Fairfield Ave. Chicago, IL 60622 (630) 346-4095 hoeckers@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Creative and self-motivated professional, with 15 years of experience as a freelance musician. Aiming to transition into a career in web development after over 2 years of study and experience building applications with actual user-bases

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

First Ascent Climbing & Fitness — Senior Operations Expert

January 2021 - PRESENT

Create internal application to manage youth program scheduling & communication, optimize existing and create new operations team workflows

Freelance Musician

2007 - PRESENT

Manage ever-changing schedule, quickly learn new material with hard deadlines, communicate professionally and effectively in a team environment

SKILLS

JavaScript (TypeScript), Ruby, Rust, SQL, React, NodeJS, HTML, CSS, Tailwind, Git

Strong written & verbal communication

Creative problem solving

EDUCATION

Launch School

2021-2023

Software Engineering

Depaul University

2007 - 2011

Music Performance